Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Driven by rage, the elves who'd been reborn as magic knights continued their vicious attack.
As the Black Bulls hurried to defend the royal capital, they crossed paths with Sally, Rades, and Valtos,
who had narrowly escaped death when Licht unexpectedly used them as a sacrifice to resurrect his elven brethren.
You get it on my nerves, too! But my first priority is killing off that bastard, Licht!
After some convincing, the trio found common ground with the Black Bulls and joined their cause.
Meanwhile, at the castle, Noelle's determination to save her siblings and protect the capital
motivated her to learn an awe-inspiring new technique.
It's over!
Why, Chris? No!
As for Finn...
Your brother! Wake up!
He finally found a way to quell the destructive rampage of his possessed brother, Longris.
But, once Patry returned to the hideout, he began to put a terrifying plan into motion.
Now all that's left is to fit the final magic stone into the pedestal within the castle, and initiate the spell that will destroy the Clover Kingdom.
After humanity is snuffed out.
We will reclaim this world, making it a peaceful place in the castle.
Now all that's left is to fit the final magic stone into the pedestal within the castle, and initiate the spell that will destroy the Clover Kingdom.
After humanity is snuffed out.
We will reclaim this world, making it a peaceful place for elves alone.
Roger that.
As soon as these two wake up, all the actors will be able to return to the castle.
Now all that's left is to fit the final magic stone into the castle.
Now all that's left is to fit the final magic stone into the pedestal within the castle, and initiate the spell that will destroy the Clover Kingdom.
After humanity is snuffed out, we will reclaim this world, making it a peaceful place for elves alone.
Roger that.
As soon as these two wake up, all the actors will be on stage.
Caitlyn
Aspetto
Oh, it mets like that
You only dare that
Again, oblige
Same with the wisdom
All I have been lost
Forget it, we won't take it
To do it, I'll fame
To do it for you
This means we survive
And I can add a mighty air to you
Na!
Do we
Who you worked for?
Yeah. We made up the Third Eye, as I recall.
Fauna the Hateful, and Vettor the Despair.
And you were called Raya the Disloyal, isn't that right?
How funny.
As the Eye of the Midnight Sun's most formidable warriors,
the Third Eye had fought multiple battles against Asta and his friends in the past.
Vettor was killed, and Fauna's soul became separated from the body it had been inhabiting,
which in turn allowed that body to begin a new life.
Raya preserved the general characteristics of the human bodies the other two had been using,
and prepared two new vessels for their souls to possess.
Welcome back, guys. I could only incubate you for so long,
so your bodies are about fifteen years old.
Which means you're smaller than me for a change, Vettor.
Well, seeing as how I've already died twice, this'll do fine.
Agreed.
Creating near-identical bodies with the same mana as the originals.
I gotta say, Sally's really outdone herself with her research on this one.
I'd compliment her, but she's probably been dead for a while now.
My mind is a lot clearer this time around, too.
Oh, I can explain that. See, last round, we used the Evil Eye to bring you back,
so I'm sure your malice was a lot stronger before.
Evil Eye? That's right. I did feel half asleep back then.
It was almost like I was having some terrible nightmare.
Salamander!
There's no response. I guess I must not have it anymore.
That means it found somebody else who was qualified while Fauna was gone and partnered up with them instead.
Eh, it's fine. Even without Salamander, you're strong enough as you are now.
Yeah, that's true. There's no way I'd let those humans beat me!
Okay, the next step is to take you over to the Grimoire Tower. The sooner you let one pick you out, the better.
Before that, we need... some clothes. Especially for her, and Quick.
He's right. Now that I take a good look, I think you're more developed than last time.
Good for you!
Before too long, this false royal capital constructed by the humans will be no more.
They've finally gathered above.
Then they must have received the revelation in preparation for this moment.
Those who guide the elves! The apostles of Sephora!
Lift, it's you!
He's not saying much. But I can guarantee you he's in there somewhere, deep down.
Trust me, Patry, as soon as the reincarnation is complete, you'll see the old licked again.
I understand. Wait, what about that boy?
Oh yeah, that was weird. He was reincarnated like us, but somehow he still kept the human's personality.
Are you serious?
Don't sweat it. He'll come around too when everything's finished. Let's go and wait over there.
Okay.
Man, get a load of this view. The party's in full swing.
Now then, let's get started.
By infusing Gravitos stones with magic, we'll open the door below Clover Castle and release the seal on the underworld.
What the hell is that?
This doesn't look good.
Nozel, what's happening to the castle?
I don't understand this at all.
This is a magic space that serves as a border between this world and the next, which the elves entrusted to the humans through an ancient pact.
It's called the Shadow Palace.
It can only be opened by the Apostles of Sephira. Ten elves who can receive divine messages. See?
When we place the final magic stone into its pedestal inside the palace, the elves' great reincarnation will be complete.
Of course, a price must be paid for our use of these bodies. Sadly, their human souls will be sent to the underworld.
Think again! As an Envoy of Beauty, I won't allow such ugliness!
David's dice magic gives him various advantages, with higher rolls being the most devastating.
But getting this much power from a two? It doesn't make sense!
It won't do you any good to attack me, but you might as well give it a shot.
How are we going to fix this?
Okay, so there's a magical space growing over there. I don't really get the details, but it's definitely bad news.
Okay, sounds like our cue to head that way.
You won't stop the Apostles of Sephira.
I get the feeling they're not planning to cooperate with us.
Show me what you've got then! I'll shut you all to smithereens!
Hang on! We can't fight that many without Finral's spatial magic!
Dammit!
It's one thing after another. Can't these jerks just give us a break?
Now what?
Hey, is that...
Here we are!
You guys are safe!
Okay, so there's a magical space growing over there.
I don't really get the details, but it's definitely bad news.
Care, care. Sounds like our cue to head that way.
You won't stop the Apostles of Sephira.
I get the feeling they're not planning to cooperate with us.
Show me what you've got then! I'll shut you all to smithereens!
Hang on! We can't fight that many without Finral's spatial magic!
Dammit!
It's one thing after another. Can't these jerks just give us a break?
Now what?
Hey! Is that...
I know this thing looks scary, but it's just us!
Also, don't freak out when you see who we brought with us. It's kind of a long story, but it's fine, I promise.
Hey, look! What's with that black castle back there?
Looks like Ghost is chilling on top of the enemy base!
Our best friend meets us.
You guys, this is so overwhelming!
Tell me where Licht is right now!
A huge bone! No way!
That's Tsar Henry.
Ha ha ha ha! You bunch of dumbasses! Better work on that entrance!
Captain! Sorry to make you late!
Whoa! Finral's behind him! Totally passed out!
Oh no! I didn't even know you woke up the first time! You can't turn around and go back to sleep already, Finral!
You'd better not make us check you into the infirmary again after you just got out.
My cooking will get everybody back in tip-top shape, so I want all of you to pile your plates up with some yummy food!
What took you guys so long? The next words out of your mouth better be thank you for picking up our slack, you lazy idiots!
It was terrifying!
Whoa! What's with the new outfit, Noelle? You look extra cool now!
You're the ones who almost got your butts kicked! You should be thanking us, princess!
You care to explain the walking house full of loud people?
I wish I could, but this is new for me, too. It seems like our squad gets weirder every day.
But everything's gonna be okay now, because all of the Black Bulls are here!
Curse you, humans! Bring in whatever reinforcements you like, you're still no match for the elves!
Ready?
This belt gauges the strength of their attack, and then together...
We intercepted!
So cool!
Now where's your leader?
That's enough! Take this!
Come on, Rouge!
What happened? Our attacks aren't landing!
Here goes!
Good! Now hurry and jow down so you can replenish all the mana you just used!
I can't use magic, but I'm gonna eat anyway!
I don't see light anywhere!
Oh, look, and I'm having a snack in the middle of a fight!
So, what do you think of my team? Pretty tough, aren't they?
I wanna cut them!
Whoa! Well, don't!
Really? The Black Bulls?
Even here, they stand in my way.
That one's magic interferes with the very laws of nature.
So she's a witch!
It would appear their defense largely depends on her.
I'm going now. Goodbye.
Oh, Rave!
I see, so you're finally awake.
I can't believe it, you sleep even more than Raya does.
You gonna be okay? This'll be your first spell in centuries, your past life included.
Are we? Yes, I'm fine.
Black Bulls, can you hear me?
Mimosa's here with her brother and that mushroom guy!
If we don't do something, all of the magic knights who've been possessed are going to lose their souls forever!
We're running out of time, Asta!
Seriously?
My! Such magnificent magic!
Don't tell me this key is what I think it is!
I know her!
That's the captain of the coral peacocks!
Did she get possessed too?
Dream magic. Glamour world.
No way!
What did she do?!
I can sense the magic of the pieces that vanished, but they don't exist anywhere.
Hey, we're missing some people! Vanessa, Magna, Luck, Charmy, Sally! What did she do with everyone?!
It's gorgeous, but the moment she activates it, her targets will cease to exist in this world!
They've been whisked away to the world of dreams! And once you're in, there's nothing you can do to get out.
There is. There must be.
Well, I suppose that takes care of their defense.
Alright, let's wrap things up then.
Combo spell. Light Sword Storm of Imperial Conviction.
Ha! There you are, let's find me!
And there's Ghost too!
Hey, Garden, could you please do that one thing now?!
Okay!
Poison curse magic, dwelling of the poison cloud!
Whoa, wait!
I don't see how this is gonna help!
Don't worry, I can fix it!
Conversion magic!
Poison the cloud!
Oh, that was close!
Thanks for saving everyone, Gray!
What were you trying to do?! Poison the whole squad?!
I was using teamwork to help my friends in their time of need.
We can handle things here.
Why don't you go ahead and meet up with your precious Licht?
I wish you wouldn't say it like that.
But yes, I'm counting on you, Draw.
Sure, I'll catch you later.
Hey, Valtos! Make me a portal!
Man, they're such jerks!
Everyone!
You should get away from me!
Henry!
He got too far away from the raging Black Bull!
And without Charmy, nobody can recharge their mana if it runs out!
You guys!
My armor! It vanished!
Well, that crazy spell of yours was kind of a doozy.
Your body probably can't keep up with it just yet.
Now that I think of it, I'm running pretty low on juice myself.
Oh, Oster!
Goodness, you look even more feeble than usual!
I know the Black Bulls need my help, but I can't let the boss man slip through my fingers.
Don't screw this up, you hear me?!
I want you to surpass your damn limits!
Oh my God, that's good!
Sounds good! I'll see you in a little bit then!
Time to go, Jack!
Sis, when am I taking orders from you?!
Look, brother. Some of them are gone.
Then we need to kill the rest of them quickly and hurry after the ones who left.
That's where you come in, Eklat. It's time for a fun game of hide-and-seek.
Right.
Willpower won't be enough to save them now.
I found them.
Look at me, humans.
Mirror magic!
Eye magic!
Combo spell reflect iris!
What's happening?!
Why can't I move?
We're stuck!
How is this possible?!
My magic!
Little Eklat has the ability to immobilize anybody who looks into her eyes.
It renders your magic useless as well.
What?!
But Marie doesn't even have her grimoire yet!
I guess the elves are just that powerful.
There's no hope for you.
Now die, helpless worms.
Not yet.
I refuse to give up!
This is not the end!
I still have to turn Goshen Marie back to normal!
Not to mention everyone else!
I'll set things right!
No matter what it takes!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
Hey, look at that!
I can move!
He must have nullified the spell.
Asta, you did it!
Okay, you guys.
Everyone ready?!
Hold on.
That blade.
Why does he have Lick's demon destroyer sword?
You don't deserve that weapon!
Give it back and die!
I'll use transformation magic!
Here!
To make more mirrors!
Poison magic!
Forbidden fruit!
It may be stronger now, but I still understand Goshen's magic really well.
Actually, he kinda ticks me off.
The way he used to shoot those weird beams at me.
You know, getting possessed didn't change his personality much.
Yes, I agree.
And after we save him, he'll go right back to insulting us.
That's exactly what'll happen!
Plus, he'll keep showing us pictures of his sister and making dolls of her and getting nosebleeds when he thinks about her!
He's really not a fun person to be around!
He's always been creepy!
That's why we need to bring back the ghost we all know!
So we can complain to his face!
She's always been richer and being bisexual!
She died during all of poker,
She'sston-
Thank you.
To be continued...
I was in a bit of a rush to take you out.
Which means your bodies are going to be pretty puny now.
Okay, I probably shouldn't have jumped the gun.
Part 2.
I had plenty of time to spare, so I let him steep.
Veto and Fauna should be more mature this time around.
I don't know what happened to me before.
We gotta find some kind of happy medium here.
My best friend, Ghosh Adlai.
Your little sister is basically my little sister.
That's right, Marie is my actual sister.
Black Clover, page 111.
The eyes in the mirror.
Ah, dear sister, I weep for you.